In the following clips we're going to talk about the proper way to repack, grease and adjust your vehicle's wheel barriers.
In this clip what I'm going to talk about is letting the vehicle down off of our jack and jack stands.
Before you do that, you want to make sure lug nuts are run down pretty much just a fuzz past hand tight.
It's going to be impossible to tark them being that the wheel free spins.
So what you're going to do is just take and hold on to it and give them a twist.
I'm going to start here, on a five bolt pattern which is 95 percent of the vehicle's out there.
You're going to go from here.
You have two choices.
This one or this one.
You're going to do it in what they call a star pattern.
We're going to go from here to the farthest one away.
Give her a little snug to the farthest one away.
We only have one choice now.
Here to the farthest one away.
Here and to the farthest one away, here.
What that will do is ensure that the wheel is torched down flat and centered.
That will eliminate any possible causes of vibration.
What I'm going to do now since I have my wheel snug is take and remove my jack stand, get that guy out of the way and release the pressure on my hydraulic floor jack.
You're going to want to let your jack creep down very slowly.
It only takes about a 10th of a turn on the release screw to open up the hydraulic circuit and allow the jack to collapse.
Once the pressure is released from the jack, you can take and roll it out of the way.
And that is the proper way to seat your wheel and let the vehicle down.